The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Demon guards, come out !
Feng Yin
Demon Guard
Demon guard Feng Yin
is here.
We're finally getting a real task.
De Gui
Demon guard
Demon guard Hu Pao
is here !
Master has ordered
the execution of Wang Lin !
Understood !
Wang Lin...
My Soul Flag is now complete !
And with the secret technique Master has given me,
I will now
kill you by my own hands !
Ancient Battlefield
Sky Demon Country
Interesting...
You do have some skill.
Taste this !
Earth Sore,
break !
Feng Yin,
you're late.
Before my Heaven Pus and Earth Sore,
he has no chance of survival.
After you're done,
quickly go back to report.
I'll take the credit for this kill !
Return !
Feng Yin !
Death Finger !
You can't escape.
That celestial palm print...
How could he know this spell ?
I have failed in my duty.
I deserve to be punished.
Among the Demon guards, the only one left
is the one who controls millions of souls
and that has the Instant Power spell.
He will surely be able to injure him.
Investigate him.
What kind of Demon
dares block Grandpa Xu's path !?
There are too many souls !
Master,
don't you think that
these spells look familiar ?
Long time no see,
Wang Lin...
You little bastard,
it was you !
Hu Pao ?
Your Excellency still remembers his discarded pawn ?
I'm grateful for that.
How should I properly repay you ?
How about...
killing you by my own hands !?
Back then, you seemed so lofty and unreachable.
But looking at you now...
You're nothing special.
Hu Pao,
why did you decide
to betray me ?
Betray you !?
You abandoned me.
You're the one that betrayed me first !
Where were you when I was thrown in that prison cell ?
When my meridians were crushed,
my bones broken,
and I suffered endless torment...
Where were you !?
I was nothing but a pawn in your hands.
If I hadn't met my Benefactor,
I would have died long ago !
However,
you don't have to worry
because I won't let you die easily.
I will throw you into the cruelest prison of the 9 countries.
I'll tear your tendons, pull out your bones,
and extract your soul to seal it into my Soul Flag !
That way you will neither live
nor die !
I owe you an apology
for leaving you back then.
I don't need it !
All I want now is to turn you
and that Soul Refining Tribe of yours
into my soul fragments !
You don't want to kill me
just because of your hatred.
Your true goal
is to kill everyone that knows the Soul Refining spell
to be the last one to know it.
Am I wrong ?
As expected of my former Master,
you're clever.
Correct !
If I'm the only person aware of this spell,
then one day
I will refine all living beings of this world !
Even the Demon Emperor
will have to kneel before me !
Unfortunately,
you are not worthy
of seeing that day happen !
One
Instant
Power !
This is...
Hundred Million Soul Devour !
Hu Pao
Demon guard
Rank 100 000 Demonic Energy
(Middle stage Soul Transformation)
Hu Pao
Demon guard
Rank 200 000 Demonic Energy
(Late stage Soul Transformation)
Hu Pao
Demon guard
Rank 300 000 Demonic Energy
(Early stage Ascendant)
For over a decade,
I cultivated day and night
in order to create this Hundred Million-Soul Flag !
Combined with the spell my Benefactor gave me,
Wang Lin,
you are no longer my match !
Die !
You are indeed very talented.
But this isn't how you use
a Soul Flag.
Without the true inheritance,
you cannot really control the souls.
Your mighty ambition
is nothing but a fool's dream.
Souls,
come back !
Impossible...
How is this possible !?
My Benefactor had clearly fixed
the flaw of the Soul Flag !
Why !?
Your Benefactor ?
If he truly cared about you,
he wouldn't have taught you this so-called Instant Power.
This sinister spell may temporarily boost your cultivation
but it drains
your lifespan and life energy.
Impossible !
When has this Benefactor of yours ever treated you properly ?
Shut up !
Shut the hell up !
Hu Pao
Demon guard
Rank 300 000 Demonic Energy
(Early stage Ascendant)
Hu Pao
Demon guard
Rank 200 000 Demonic Energy
(Late stage Soul Transformation)
Hu Pao
Demon guard
Rank 100 000 Demonic Energy
(Middle stage Soul Transformation)
You...
Your luck has run out.
It's all your fault.
You ruined me !
I'll kill you !
I'll kill you !!
Since you rebelled because of me,
before you die
I shall let you see the true power of the Soul Flag.
It was my lack of foresight
I didn't expect
that he had left a failsafe in the Soul Refining spell.
That's why...
it failed in the end.
Don't worry.
He fought his way here single-handedly
and has already given me many surprises.
However, Ming Yuan,
what is your cultivation level ?
Late stage Ascendant
The Demon Tower was given to me by Master,
it's essential for my revival
so you must not fail.
My patience is limited.
Do you understand ?
Master, I understand !
I'll do everything I can
to kill this man.
The effects of the Celestial Ascension Fruits
are beginning to fade.
Late stage Ascendant...
Since I have come here,
there's no turning back.
So you really managed to fight your way here on your own.
I commend your courage.
But
that was foolish !
Dao of...
the Underworld !
Wind !
Impressive...
You do have a sliver of comprehension of the Dao.
However...
Rain !
A physical form of demonic energy ?
As expected of a Late stage Ascendant cultivator.
But killing me
isn't that easy.
Condense the River's Soul !
Celestial Slaughter Art !
To be able to use your comprehension of the Dao to break my spell...
that means you're at your limit !
Such concentrated demonic energy...
Let me show you
the true might of the demonic path !
Even if you use all your tricks,
you'll merely block a single strike.
Wang Lin,
you can't kill me.
But I
can destroy you !
Who said
that I wanted to kill you ?
This is...
Ling Tianhou's sword !?
From the very beginning,
my target
has never been you.
You're courting death !
Tell your master
to come out !
What a vindictive little brat !
You never cease to surprise me.
He's here.
Ming Yuan,
you have disappointed me.
Master, spare...
I've been in this armor for so long
that I almost forgot
what having a body feels like.
Such pressure...
This person's cultivation
is above Ascendant !
What makes you think
that you can fight me ?
Alright,
I'll give you 5 breaths to flee.
In that case...
Since you have a death wish,
I shall grant it !
Damn you !
It's you !
An Ascendant self-detonation ?
Even if your body and soul explode,
you won't kill me !
Explode !
You're a complete madman !
Madman ?
If someone messes with me,
I will destroy them !
A complete madman !
He gave up his life to destroy my Demon Tower !
My countless years of accumulating energy
were destroyed in an instant !
“When I was under the influence of the Celestial Ascension Fruits, I was able to create this underworld river with my Dao. Now that I’m sober, I’m still able to condense the soul of the river!”
The 100 million soul fragments fused with the underworld river and fused into one. This soul was the soul of the Underworld River!
The Underworld River now had a soul, so it suddenly moved when the wind, rain, thunder, and lightning descended from the sky. Wang Lin was inside the Underworld River. He spread out his Divine Sense and his Dao fused with the river. At this moment, his Origin Soul let out a roar and the Underworld river Charged into the sky.
Now that it had a soul, the Underworld River seemed to have gained intelligence. It was like a dragon, as it let out a roar and wanted to devour the wind, rain, thunder, and lightning spell!
At the same time, 130 000 strands of slaughter energy came out from between Wang Lin’s eyebrows and fused with the dragon. Now this Underworld River carried killing intent!
This was Wang Lin’s real Underworld River. It contained 130 000 strands of slaughter energy, 100 million soul fragments, and Wang Lin’s Dao!
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.